(Leonard:)It'll be fun.
Like a clown car. Heh, heh.
(Penny:)-Hang on.
-Hm, yeah? What? Huh?
(Penny:)We just broke up.
(Leonard:)You and me? Yeah, we did.
(Leonard:)Not too long ago.
How are you doing with it?
(Penny:)Not as good as you, apparently.
(Leonard:)I don't follow.
You know, it's none of my business.
You wanna sleep with Sheldon's buddy
right after we broke up, go for it.
(Leonard:)-Well, now--
SHELDON: Excuse me.
(Sheldon:)I'm uncomfortable
with you recommending...
...Leonard pursue intercourse
with Dr. Plimpton.
(Sheldon:)Who, I assure you,
has better things to do.
(Penny:)I'm not recommending it.
(Penny:)I'm saying it already happened.
Oh, that's preposterous.
(Sheldon:)Tell her, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Well....
(Raj:)No.
Oh, come on. It wasn't my fault.
(Sheldon:)The implication being that you somehow
tripped and fell into her lady parts?
(Penny:)I'm just gonna take the bus to work.
(Leonard:)-Penny, I can still drive you.
-No, no, it's okay.